goodmockups.com 2017-12-23

# Privacy Statement - Good Mockups

### This Privacy Policy Discloses Goodmockups.com

READ THE POLICY CAREFULLY BEFORE USING AND SURFING OUR WEBSITE, YOU ACKNOWLEDGE THAT YOU HAVE READ, AGREE TO BE ASSURED TO ALL THE TERMS AND CONDITIONS OF THIS DOCUMENT.

IF YOU DO NOT AGREE TO OUR TERMS OF USAGE, PLEASE CLOSE THIS PAGE.

  1. ### Changes to Privacy Statement:

This privacy policy document can be changed / edited at any time by us after revising the website’s privacy. Once the revised document is up and live on our website, it will become operative instantly. It is your responsibility to revisit the statement and read it again carefully.

  2. ### Users Information Collection:

Personal identification is used as well as the cookies data is collected to improve our submissions. We can also use your comments, subscription or feedback to use in our marketing materials later. We also collect visitors’ data to analyze trends, gather search information and demographics to improve our website.

  3. ### Personal Information Release

Visitors’ information is not shared with 3rd parties but we may share the information in house for our protection and to protect others.

  4. ### Security

Security measures are taken to protect the information. All passwords are encrypted and we recommend you not to share any information with anyone else. Your personal information will stay secured in our servers. We have a full time dedicated and professional team which handles and manages security 24/7.

  5. ### Data Tracking

To satisfy user experience, we collect cookies which are stored in your computer. A cookie is a small file which includes all the user searched data. The data is used by our website to tract and target user interests in order to deliver the best experience. It helps a user save a lot of time and displays the best possible information that user is searching. Nowadays, browsers collect cookies automatically but you can change or decline the collection of cookies in your browser.

  6. ### Contacting Us

We would like to stay connected with our users as your feedback will let us help improve our website etc. Your suggestions are always welcome.
